<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Danyal Saqib</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Danyal Saqib</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m a MSc student at the University of Calgary&amp;rsquo;s Department of Mechanical and Manufacturing Engineering, where I do research focusing on the development of Compliant Control methods for Human-Robot Interaction, via adaptive control policies and learning algorithms. My supervisor is Dr. Marie Charbonneau.
I previously completed my Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Electrical Engineering from the School of Electrical Engineering and Computer Science at the National University of Sciences and Technology. My Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Thesis focused on a self-supervised robotic grasping setup.</description></item><item><title>Privacy policy</title><link>/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/privacy/</guid><description>Links to other websites Other websites referenced here may collect information about you, use cookies, embed additional tracking services from third parties, and record your interaction with that embedded content, including your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are signed in to that website.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/</guid><description>Selected Projects Scalable Self-Supervised Learning for Robotic Grasping
Danyal Saqib, Salman Nasir, Obaid-ur-Rahman, Abdul Mohaiman Hashmi
This is my Bachelor’s thesis. We created a scalable robotic setup that automates both the collection of data, dataset labelling, and the training of the Neural Network for grasping. Based on papers published by Alex Krizhevsky and Abhinav Gupta. Unbiased Scene Graph Generation
Danyal Saqib
An implementation of an unbiased scene graph generator using Kaihua Tang’s published papers and github repository as references.</description></item></channel></rss>